[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "What do we know about the person that perpetrated this hideous crime?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "know", "about", "the", "person", "that", "perpetrated", "this", "hideous", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "You know, it is so heart-breaking, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "is", "so", "heart-breaking", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Danbury", "Newtown"]}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What can you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, obviously it's been a horrific day in the greater Danbury area and particularly the town of Newtown.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "horrific", "day", "in", "the", "greater", "Danbury", "area", "and", "particularly", "the", "town", "of", "Newtown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Did you know if there plans for more vigils tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "if", "there", "plans", "for", "more", "vigils", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "There are vigils scheduled throughout this community, Newtown, throughout weekend.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "vigils", "scheduled", "throughout", "this", "community", ",", "Newtown", ",", "throughout", "weekend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "When was the first you heard about this and how did you hear?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "first", "you", "heard", "about", "this", "and", "how", "did", "you", "hear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I received a call from the school system from the superintendent saying that there was a shooting in Newtown, but didn't say it was a school, that the schools were on lockdown.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "received", "a", "call", "from", "the", "school", "system", "from", "the", "superintendent", "saying", "that", "there", "was", "a", "shooting", "in", "Newtown", ",", "but", "did", "n't", "say", "it", "was", "a", "school", ",", "that", "the", "schools", "were", "on", "lockdown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "When you got there, obviously scenes of complete chaos, how quickly was it that you realized your daughter was safe?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "got", "there", ",", "obviously", "scenes", "of", "complete", "chaos", ",", "how", "quickly", "was", "it", "that", "you", "realized", "your", "daughter", "was", "safe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Can you hear?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "hear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Is this something you could have predicted he would one day flip and do something as monstrous as this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "something", "you", "could", "have", "predicted", "he", "would", "one", "day", "flip", "and", "do", "something", "as", "monstrous", "as", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I don't know if you can ever predict something like that would happen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "you", "can", "ever", "predict", "something", "like", "that", "would", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Was he sociable?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "sociable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I always saw him alone when he was walking through the school or when he was sitting at the table, or sitting on the bus.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "always", "saw", "him", "alone", "when", "he", "was", "walking", "through", "the", "school", "or", "when", "he", "was", "sitting", "at", "the", "table", ",", "or", "sitting", "on", "the", "bus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "How would you describe his personality?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "his", "personality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "He was really quiet.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "really", "quiet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Did you know his family, his mother in particular?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "his", "family", ",", "his", "mother", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I mean, I knew her because we lived in the neighborhood.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "knew", "her", "because", "we", "lived", "in", "the", "neighborhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Were you aware of that having a big impact on him?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "aware", "of", "that", "having", "a", "big", "impact", "on", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "I don't know when they got divorced.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "when", "they", "got", "divorced", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What was your immediate reaction when you discovered it was this person you knew?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "immediate", "reaction", "when", "you", "discovered", "it", "was", "this", "person", "you", "knew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "It was devastating.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "devastating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to Adam Lanza?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "spoke", "to", "Adam", "Lanza", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Probably middle school.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "middle", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What is the possible background to what is going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "possible", "background", "to", "what", "is", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "You know, working on a lot of these cases, there a number of different causes that can be divided into two broad categories.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "working", "on", "a", "lot", "of", "these", "cases", ",", "there", "a", "number", "of", "different", "causes", "that", "can", "be", "divided", "into", "two", "broad", "categories", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Are people like this as likely to carry out what they end up doing, these atrocities, if they didn't have easy access to firearms?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "people", "like", "this", "as", "likely", "to", "carry", "out", "what", "they", "end", "up", "doing", ",", "these", "atrocities", ",", "if", "they", "did", "n't", "have", "easy", "access", "to", "firearms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Look, there is no question that firearms play a role.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "there", "is", "no", "question", "that", "firearms", "play", "a", "role", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Where do you start with trying to counsel young children when this kind of appalling thing happens?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "start", "with", "trying", "to", "counsel", "young", "children", "when", "this", "kind", "of", "appalling", "thing", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I think the first thing is helping the parents.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "first", "thing", "is", "helping", "the", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Why he would then, having killed his mother, go to the school and do what he did?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "he", "would", "then", ",", "having", "killed", "his", "mother", ",", "go", "to", "the", "school", "and", "do", "what", "he", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "You know, I don't have a crystal ball and I haven't diagnosed or assessed him.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "crystal", "ball", "and", "I", "have", "n't", "diagnosed", "or", "assessed", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Frank?", "question_tokens": ["Frank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I'd like to endorse that also.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "like", "to", "endorse", "that", "also", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What would you like to see in terms of specific gun control?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "to", "see", "in", "terms", "of", "specific", "gun", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, there a number of pieces of legislation that we have been pushing for years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "a", "number", "of", "pieces", "of", "legislation", "that", "we", "have", "been", "pushing", "for", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Can I follow-through on the Australia thing?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "follow-through", "on", "the", "Australia", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "ORGAN: No, I want you to answer this.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "No", ",", "I", "want", "you", "to", "answer", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Allowing, therefore, a clearly deranged son to take them and commit this atrocity?", "question_tokens": ["Allowing", ",", "therefore", ",", "a", "clearly", "deranged", "son", "to", "take", "them", "and", "commit", "this", "atrocity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Whatever that gun looks like, it's a semiautomatic rifle.", "answer_tokens": ["Whatever", "that", "gun", "looks", "like", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "semiautomatic", "rifle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "It's time for change?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "time", "for", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Right, it is time.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "it", "is", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Time to do what?", "question_tokens": ["Time", "to", "do", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "To get rid of some of these gun laws that cause --", "answer_tokens": ["To", "get", "rid", "of", "some", "of", "these", "gun", "laws", "that", "cause", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "To get rid of the gun laws?", "question_tokens": ["To", "get", "rid", "of", "the", "gun", "laws", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Look at what has happened, all these attacks this year have occurred where guns are banned.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "at", "what", "has", "happened", ",", "all", "these", "attacks", "this", "year", "have", "occurred", "where", "guns", "are", "banned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What has that got to do with it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "that", "got", "to", "do", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "You never let me explain.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "never", "let", "me", "explain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Can I say something?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "say", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "-- gun-free zone.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "gun-free", "zone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, I believe those of us who are licensed to carry, are responsible people, shouldn't be prohibited from carrying in schools or other places.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "those", "of", "us", "who", "are", "licensed", "to", "carry", ",", "are", "responsible", "people", ",", "should", "n't", "be", "prohibited", "from", "carrying", "in", "schools", "or", "other", "places", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WRB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Why on Earth would you want more guns in schools after what happened today?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "on", "Earth", "would", "you", "want", "more", "guns", "in", "schools", "after", "what", "happened", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Here's why, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "why", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "What were your feelings?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "your", "feelings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "It's -- it's impossible to put words to what I really feel.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "impossible", "to", "put", "words", "to", "what", "I", "really", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Do you wish after what happened to you and to Josh that tougher laws had been brought in after that to try and do something about this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "after", "what", "happened", "to", "you", "and", "to", "Josh", "that", "tougher", "laws", "had", "been", "brought", "in", "after", "that", "to", "try", "and", "do", "something", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "You know, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "You know, to be honest, it's heartbreaking.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "to", "be", "honest", ",", "it", "'s", "heartbreaking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "What are your views about the debate that will now unfold on this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "views", "about", "the", "debate", "that", "will", "now", "unfold", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "I mean, I think the president said we need a meaningful action now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "the", "president", "said", "we", "need", "a", "meaningful", "action", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "121214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "What do you feel today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "I think in the wake of today, a referendum on guns is needed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "in", "the", "wake", "of", "today", ",", "a", "referendum", "on", "guns", "is", "needed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]